ministryofhemp.com 2019-07-26

# Privacy Policy – Ministry of Hemp

Current policy effective as of Sep 12, 2018

## Purpose

* * *

The purpose of this Privacy Policy is to inform you about how Ministry of Hemp may collect, use, and disclose personal information from you and other users of the Site.

## What Information Do We Collect?

* * *

We collect information from you when you place an order, subscribe to our newsletter, respond to a survey or fill out a form.

When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your: name, e-mail address, mailing address, phone number or credit card information. You may, however, visit our site anonymously.

## What Do We Use Your Information For?

* * *

Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:

To personalize your experience: Your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs)  
To improve our website: We continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you  
To improve customer service: Your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs  
To process transactions  
To administer a contest, promotion, survey or other site feature  
To send periodic emails  
The email address you provide for order processing, may be used to send you information and updates pertaining to your order, in addition to receiving occasional company news, updates, related product or service information, etc.

Note: If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, we include detailed unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of each email.

Your information, whether public or private, will not be sold, exchanged, transferred, or given to any other company for any reason whatsoever, without your consent, other than for the express purpose of delivering the purchased product or service requested.

## Security

* * *

We take steps to safeguard your information in accordance with this Privacy Policy. For example, when you enter sensitive Personal Information such as your credit card number via the Site, we encrypt that information using secure socket layer technology (SSL).

However, no method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure. As such, we cannot promise, ensure, or warrant the security of any information that you may provide to us. We likewise do not accept liability for unintentional disclosure or data breach.

We will make any legally required disclosures of any breach of the security, confidentiality, or integrity of your unencrypted electronically stored “personal data” (as defined in applicable state statutes concerning security breach notifications) to you via email or conspicuous posting on the Site as promptly as possible, and without unreasonable delay, taking into account the legitimate needs of law enforcement or any measures necessary to determine the scope of the breach and/or to restore the reasonable integrity of the affected data system.

## Online Advertisements

* * *

Our company may display online advertisements. In those cases we share aggregated and non-identifying information about our Visitors and Customers collected through the registration process as well as through online surveys and promotions with these advertisers.

Additionally, in some instances, we use this aggregated and non-identifying information to deliver tailored advertisements. For instance, an advertiser tells us the audience they want to reach and provides us an advertisement tailored to the audience. Based upon the aggregated and non-identifying information we have collected, we may then display or send the advertisement to the intended audience. Our company does not share personal information about its Visitors or Customers with these advertisers.

## Responses To Email Inquiries

* * *

When Visitors or Customers send email inquiries to our company, the return email address is used to answer the email inquiry we receive. Our company does not use the return email address for any other purpose and does not share the return email address with any third party.

## Do We Use Cookies?

* * *

Yes. A “cookie” is a small data file that can be placed on your hard drive when you visit certain Web sites. Our company may use cookies to collect, store, and sometimes track information for statistical purposes to improve the products and services we provide and to manage our telecommunications networks.

If you are a Visitor or Customer, we may use a cookie to save your settings and to provide customizable and personalized services. These cookies do not enable third parties to access any of your customer information. Additionally, be aware that if you visit other Web sites where you are prompted to log in or that are customizable, you may be required to accept cookies.

Advertisers and partners may also use their own cookies. We do not control use of these cookies and expressly disclaim responsibility for information collected through them.

## Children

* * *

The Site does not knowingly target children under the age of 13, and Ministry of Hemp does not collect Personal Information from any child under the age of 13. If we learn that any such information has been provided to us via the Site, we will delete or destroy it. If you believe that Personal Information about your child or another child under the age of 13 has been transmitted through the Site, please contact us.

## Disclosing Information To Outside Parties

* * *

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

## California Privacy Rights

* * *

Because we value your privacy we have taken the necessary precautions to be in compliance with the California Online Privacy Protection Act. We therefore will not distribute your personal information to outside parties without your consent.

## Your Consent

* * *

By using our site, you consent to our privacy policy.

## Revisions

* * *

Our company reserves the right to revise, amend, or modify this policy, our Terms Of Service agreement, and our other policies and agreements at any time and in any manner, by updating this posting.

## Questions?

* * *

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, or if you have suggestions on how we might improve it, please contact us at info@ministryofhemp.com.

(Visited 273 times, 50 visits today)
